<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Eportfolios on Atharva Naik GLP Portfolio</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Eportfolios on Atharva Naik GLP Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.125.5</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fall 2021 - Spring 2022: Student Retention and Engagement</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/pdl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/pdl/</guid><description>During my second year in GLP, I had the chance to apply HCD internally to improve the program. As part of the Student Retention and Engagement committee, my task was to set up GLP for long-term success: make sure students stay in the program and find ways to recruit new students.
In order to do this, my committee created a comprehensive marketing plan, along with laying the groundwork for an extensive social media presence.</description></item><item><title>Fall 2022: Illinois Global Summit</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/igs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/igs/</guid><description>Because of my involvement in GLP, I was selected as one of the only student moderators for the Illinois Global Summit. This was a one-day symposium upholding the Vision 2030 Global Strategy, and I was in charge of moderating the final panel of the symposium titled &amp;ldquo;Supporting Youth Development for Global Change.&amp;rdquo; This panel discussed how fostering youth engagement across disciplines is critical to developing the next generation of global problem solvers.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2021: Champaign-Urbana Public Health District</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/cuphd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/cuphd/</guid><description>During my first year in GLP (2020-2021), also the first-year of the program itself, my group was tasked with working with the Champaign-Urbana Public Health District (CUPHD) as our community sponsor. Our design challenge was to research and ideate best practices for building community capacity (using both local and international models) to address mental health during COVID-19, to determine what our next steps should be to build capacity for our community, by our community in CU.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2023: Annual Conference on the First-Year Experience</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/fye/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/fye/</guid><description>In my junior year of GLP, I had the honor of being selected as one of three students in the program to present at the prestigous Annual Conference on the First-Year Experience hosted in Los Angeles by the University of South Carolina.
When we arrived at the conference in LA, we quickly realized that we were some of the only students there. Regardless of this fact, our presence in various conference sessions was welcomed, and our unique perspective was respected.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2023: HCD Crash Course</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/vctb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/vctb/</guid><description>In Spring 2023, me and a team of GLP students worked with VC_TB, a Brazillian language learning app in order to help them better understand and implement HCD into their everyday internal and external operations. This research aimed to provide practical recommendations for the company to integrate a human-centered design approach that puts users at the center of their services and problem-solving practices. Human-Centered design (HCD) is an approach to design that prioritizes the needs, preferences, and experiences of users and stakeholders.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2024: GLP Graduation Certificate and Pin</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/grad_cert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/grad_cert/</guid><description>In my final semester in GLP, I helped create the first ever GLP Graduation Certificate and Pin.</description></item><item><title>Spring 2024: LAS 195, LAS 399 Teaching Assistantship</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/ta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/ta/</guid><description>For my capstone project, I served as the TA for the LAS 195 and LAS 399 GLP classes. I was the primary instructor for LAS 195 and handled all workshop logistics, grading, and project support. I also presented a 90-minute interactive workshop on tech for social good. For LAS 399, I facilitated in-class discussions and presented a 90-minute interactive professional interview workshop.
Learnings as a TA Presentation skills by leading two workshops - one on Tech for Social Good and one on Professional Interviews.</description></item><item><title>Winter 2022-2023: GLP Appalachia Trip</title><link>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/appalachia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atharvanaik10.github.io/eportfolio/appalachia/</guid><description>Over the winter of 2022, I had the chance to travel to the Binns-Counts Community Center in McClure, Virginia. This was a standout experience in GLP because I truly got to see the underbelly of America.
During this three-day trip, we travelled to various towns in the Appalachians, learning about their culture and meeting the people. In particular, we attended a bluegrass concert, visited a local church, and went to a the Mountain Hertiage Museum.</description></item></channel></rss>